Ayushi Kandari ayushikandari0206@gmail.com



+91 8218762528



CATALOG ASSOCIATE



PROI

Customer-oriented, German catalog associate with an Established track record in catalog management and Proficiency in troubleshooting in EU/UK markets and Organizing meetings with stakeholders and brand managers to enhance performance and efficiency. Experienced in translating German to English, root cause analysis, problem-solving, and keeping precise catalog information to improve customer experience.

Languages

Hindi

English

German

Spanish

Skills

Catalog maintenance

Detail page management

Microsoft Office

German to English translation

Microsoft excel

Communication Skills

Microsoft PowerPoint

Invoice processing and verification

Data analysis

Project Management

Customer service management

Hobbies

- · Horse Riding
- **Content Creation**
- **Dancing**
- Reading

Work Experience

German Catalog Associate

05/2022 - Present | Bangalore

Amazon India

- Currently Working as a German Catalog Associate at Amazon India.
- Addressing and Handling problems in catalogs across the EU/UK and making decisions to prevent any divergences from SOP.
- organizing daily meetings with brands, and retail managers, as well as with junior interns.
- Interacting with brand managers based on product defect rates and assisting in resolving issues.
- Making weekly reports on troubleshooting activities and delivering weekly presentations on performance.
- prioritizing customer satisfaction to improve product viewing simplicity and user-friendliness.
- · Handling and updating catalog details such as title, core description, images, etc.

Quality Assurance Trainee

01/2022 - 03/2022 | Noida

Boketto Technology

- Done a Three-month internship as a Trainee Quality Analyst within the Swiggy process.
- Worked in a chat-based environment to Ensure the SOP of the company.
- Collaborated with delivery executives and business personnel to troubleshoot and resolve various challenges they encountered during delivery and ensure smooth operations to provide customer satisfaction.

Associate Intern

09/2021 - 12/2021 | Noida

Q Connegt

- Completed a Three-month internship and gained invaluable experience in addressing customer queries within the Dr. Path Labs (Voice process English).
- In this internship, I have acquired communication skills and Knowledge of working in business and the importance of SOP by actively dealing with clients, taking business orders, and guiding them about business.

Education

Amity University

HIGH SCHOOL

Delhi Public School(DPS)

05/2018 - 05/2019 | Dehradun

Activities

- Completed coursework in NTCC-(Non-Teaching Credit Course) involves conducting a thesis or individual project. It begins with topic selection, followed by in-depth research and the drafting of a research paper.
- Awarded for excellence in interschool dance competition.
- Recognized for exceptional achievements in both interschool and debate competitions.
- Involved in making content about travel and lifestyle with more than 6000 followers on Instagram.
- Skilled horse rider with skills and knowledge in horse riding and related Tasks